It is Tuesday here on the Amanda Seale Show. It's time for the Big Up Letdown.
Amanda, who are you saluting today?
Goes to the Alabama high school students who walked out over Black History Month erasure.
You know, I don't know if y'all really noticed, but everything that we learned about in civil rights class and in history class in the 60s,
it's happening again because it's happening again.
More than 200 students walked out of class at an Alabama high school after they were told by school leaders to admit certain relevant events from an upcoming student-led Black History Month program.
Why? Because apparently there was an administrator who said it made them feel uncomfortable for them to mention actual historical moments, including slavery and the civil rights movement.
This was a program that was scheduled for February 22nd.
It is Black History Month, so of course it makes sense that you would do a history event about Black history in a legitimate way.
The students were told they couldn't talk about slavery and civil rights because they were uncomfortable.
And they were like, you know what? The students were told they couldn't talk about slavery and civil rights.
And they were like, oh, word? Guess what? Black History Month program board member Janiah Suttles, a senior, said, we walking out.
And I really feel like this is such a big up because the students, they were the ones that also led us in the 60s, okay?
So to see this made me say, man, it sucks that this is happening again.
But I think it's great that we're seeing the students say, now we have the power and we're going to take it.